

#### CONTACT

- +62 877-6263-8070
- Jember, East Java
- irvanjunaidi2@gmail.com
- ( @irvanswan
- in linkedin.com/in/irvan-junaidi

#### SKILLS

- JavaScript
- SOL
- ReactJS
- ExpressJS
- NextJS
- PHP
- Code Igniter

## CERTIFICATION

- Junior Web Development (2020 -2023)
- Dekstop Application Traingin Professional Level (2020)
- Junior Mobile Promgrammer (2019 2022)

# **IRVAN JUNAIDI**

## FULL-STACK WEB DEVELOPER

#### PERSONAL PROFILE

I am a Full-Stack Web Developer who is very interested in web development and I want to continue to grow in programming skills. My technical skill is on React JS (Framework Frontend), Express JS (Framework Backend), Javascript, PHP, Code Igniter. I have experience in building web applications.

#### **EDUCATION HISTORY**

# **Bootcamp Fazztrack**

Talent Full-Stack Web Developer | February 2021 - Agustus 2021

- Studied project planning, coordination, and ethics
- Building website with Express JS, React JS and Next JS

# Politeknik Negeri of Jember

College Student | July 2017 - Dec 2020

- GPA: 3.68
- Ahli Madya Komputer (A. Md.Kom.)
- Program Studi Diploma Tiga Manajement Informatika

#### WORK EXPERIENCE

# Web Development

SIMS Yogyakarta | 2018 - 2019

Building website for tower of telecomuncation with PHP native

## Front-End Development

PT. Chameleon | 2021 - now

Building web app using ReactJS and NextJS

#### ORGANIZATION EXPERIENCE

# Leader of Biro Game Development

HMJ-TI (Himpunan Mahasiswa Jurusan - Teknologi Informasi) (2018 - 2019)

- Sharing about how to making game with construct 2
- Make game from construct 2 with many people
- Head of the tournament game event committee

#### Member of Biro Kesekretariatan

HMJ-TI (Himpunan Mahasiswa Jurusan - Teknologi Informasi) (2017 - 2018)

- Managed complex projects from start to finish
- Collaborated with other designers
- Translated requirements into polished, high-level designs